I think…I’m falling for someone.
I also have someone that I like.
Someone told me to give this to you.
It must come from the same person
who left you the note.
Why did you cheer on our opponent team?
Don’t you think this is too much?
He scores a goal.
Here.
A reward for a hero.
Thanks.
(The most valuable thing is time.)
(We are halfway through our high school life.)
(To get to know a person is to understand their world.)
I’ll take this desk.
Hi.
Tle, you are wearing braces.
I’ve been wearing them since last year.
Is that so?
Sorry, I’m busy with my own stuff.
So I don’t pay much attention
to other people’s lives.
(It takes around 200 hours
for a friendship to grow into a close one.)
Achi, hit me.
No.
Come on. Hit me.
Why do I need to do that?
Achi, you’re killing the fun.
Fine.
Ouch! Achi, it hurts.
(If you want to cross the friend zone,
theoretically, it takes around 2 – 4 months.)
Ko Neung, Ko Song is not here yet?
(Surprisingly, it takes only 7 seconds to fall for someone.)
(The person who makes me realize this is this guy.)
You look different when you wear glasses.
You look cool, calm, and charming.
Ko Song, you are short-sighted?
Yes, a little.
I’m worried that I can’t see the blackboard.
But I’m wearing glasses only in class.
Let me take a good look at you.
What are you doing?
I want to see if you look more handsome,
like they say.
So?
Not really.
I spent the school break
at my house in another province.
When I get back,
you all look different.
You’re right.
You guys have changed a lot.
Ko Song is wearing glasses.
Augar is now a school athlete.
Achi got a new phone.
August…
I’m taking my studies seriously now.
Fine.
But why am I still the same?
Then you should start paying attention in class.
If you don’t like studying,
why don’t you find something that you like?
I found it.
What I like.
This.
I like eating.
What?
Do you want to have some?
What are you doing?
Are you wearing perfume to school?
Is the scent that strong?
No, it’s a light scent.
But if I get closer, the scent will be stronger.
Here, here, right here.
The scent is strong.
Do you like it?
Yes, it smells good.
Hey, come here. I saved a spot for you.
Sorry. My friend saved a spot for me.
What will we order?
Augar, do we still have a practice this evening?
Achi, you haven’t had lunch?
The cafeteria is crowded.
Hey, I’m here.
The teacher dismisses my class so late.
Yes, so late.
Excuse me.
Yes.
There is a line.
Why aren’t you lining up?
Many people are waiting in line.
Don’t you feel any shame
about cutting the line?
Easy.
I saved spots in the line for my friends.
What about others waiting in line?
Don’t be so serious about it?
That’s right.
I think you should go to the back of the line.
You are ruining the reputation
of Grade 12 students.
There’s no need to be serious about this.
Fine, we’ll leave.
Please follow the line.
What’s wrong, Boss Ko?
I just noticed something.
Look.
Everyone seems to have a boyfriend or a girlfriend.
Some of them are in different classes.
Some of them are in the same class,
but their seats are apart.
But they are having lunch together.
So what?
I thought you would come to meet us tomorrow.
You know? Achi just scolded senior students.
He was waiting in line to buy his lunch.
But Grade 12 students cut in line
in front of him.
So he slapped them in the face.
Damn, did he really slap them?
He almost punched them.
He hit them in the face.
Achi, you are savage.
Augar is exaggerating it.
I just told them
that they were wrong to do that.
Yeah, I just want to make it
sound more exciting.
You read too much manga, Augar.
Me?
Are you sure?
Don’t you feel good saying it out?
Yeah.
But I was a bit scared.
There’s no need to be scared.
You didn’t do anything wrong.
Well done, Achi.
You are brave.
That’s why you are in my gang.
But the gang leader is a total mess.
Augar!
I’ll show you what I can do
when the chance comes.
What are you up to now?
I feel so good that we don’t have any classes
on the first day of school.
Why don’t you come
to watch my basketball practice?
Are you going to start the practice today?
In our dad’s days,
Michael Jordan was the star.
Now, it’s Kobe Bryant.
Do you know who will be the star
in the next four years?
Who?
Me.
Damn, you are so cool.
Augar, I know you can do it.
You are blindly supporting him.
But I think you can do it.
You work hard.
Me too. I think you can do it.
But I just can’t stand you sometimes.
Stop it, jackass.
I’m going to eat my lunch. I’m hungry.
Why are girls crazy about athletes, Ko Song?
Do they look cool?
I don’t know.
Maybe they have this charm
of knowing what they want to do.
What about you?
Did you find what you like?
Or do you have someone that you like?
I don’t know.
I only think about studying.
That’s true.
Ko Neung, did you find what you like?
Ko Song.
My friend asked me to give you this drink.
Our friend with glasses has a secret admirer.
Are you sure?
Did she say Ko Neung or Ko Song?
Don’t forget to finish the glass, Ko Song.
Thank you.
Ko Song is so cute.
Now, you’ve all grown up.
You became popular, Ko Song.
Ko Song, you are something.
An older girl has a crush on you.
If you date her, please tell her that
you have a friend named August.
He is single.
Stop it. I don’t even know who she is.
Hey.
Are you interested in her?
I’m thirsty.
Hey.
Now I know…
what I want to do.
I want to date.
Orange.
Why do you want to date?
Look at you guys.
You have all grown up
and changed in your own ways.
That’s why you want to date?
Why? Can’t I date?
No.
I have no problem with it.
I’m just curious.
Or you don’t want me to date anyone?
No.
Right?
You’re afraid that
you have to go home alone, right?
No, I just feel for your date
for having a silly boyfriend.
Boo!
Ko Song, get back here.
I forgot my bag.
Come back.
You can’t run away from me.
Do I need to close the door?
Yes.
Damn, can I use your computer?
I really want to use it. Please, please.
Yeah.
I won’t sleep tonight.
Aren’t your parents home?
They are probably upstairs.
Your house always looks like nobody is home.
If it’s my house,
I haven’t even stepped into the house,
my mom already told me to take a shower.
It’s so boring.
My house is more boring.
Really?
I guess they are boring in different ways.
Your house is lively.
You are close to your parents.
That’s why you are a cheerful person.
Maybe.
I don’t know.
I’ll play games.
I got it. I got it.
Damn, I’m dead.
What the heck?
I just started, but I’m already killed.
Look.
Hello, Dad.
When did you get home?
7.30 p.m.
You’ve been home for a while.
Why haven’t you taken a shower yet?
You need to go to bed at 10 p.m.
You have to go to school tomorrow.
Yes, Dad.
Goodbye.
Orange, you can continue to play the game.
My dad only came downstairs this time.
He will come down again in the morning.
I don’t think it’s a good idea.
Don’t you see his icy glare?
I should go home now.
Okay.
Thanks.
Thanks for what?
For playing games at my house.
If you didn’t come here,
my house would be very quiet.
How about this?
You go to my house in the morning.
I’ll come to your house in the evening.
What do you think?
It’s fair, right?
I’ll think about it.
Okay.
I’m leaving.
Hey.
If you want to talk to me.
See you.
Bye.
Here comes the hot soup.
Have a seat.
Here is your favorite. I remember.
Good.
I’m heading out to the sea soon.
Do you want…
No.
Ko, can you let me finish first?
Why are you mentioning it?
You can use minors under 18
as your laborers.
Otherwise, I’ll report you
to the Department of Labor.
Am I dreaming, honey?
Our son has all grown up.
He even knows this stuff.
He’s now in Grade 11.
Of course.
Do you have a girlfriend?
What girlfriend? No.
Didn’t you say you wanted to…
What, Ko?
Tell me now.
I have nothing to tell you, Mom.
I don’t have a girlfriend.
He doesn’t have a girlfriend, but he wants to.
Mom.
Is it that strange if I want to date?
I’m not saying anything.
Yeah.
Dad, I’m curious
what kind of boyfriend he will be.
Don’t worry, Mom.
If I’m dating,
I will introduce that person to you.
You will bring her home?
Yes.
Then what?
So you guys can get to know each other.
What are you going to do? Show me.
Yes, show me.
Dad.
Mom.
This is Ko Song, my boyfriend.
Who are your parents?
Mom, you’re watching too much soap opera.
Fine. I’ll start again.
What do you like to eat?
I like winter melon soup.
What, Mom? Just say it.
How would I know what you want me to do?
You fail it.
She tries to tell you to put food on his plate.
Yes, Ko.
This is important. You can’t forget it.
Look at your dad.
He always does that for me.
It’s not a big deal.
This is just a hypothetical scenario.
Here is your winter melon.
Please enjoy it, Ko Song.
Well done, sweetie.
I’m so proud of you, my son.
You are too into this story.
We are going to learn about internal organs today.
Please open your book.
Krittin.
Yes.
Stand up.
Do you really like oranges?
Stand on one leg.
Put the orange on your head.
What orange are you talking about?
Do it.
I’m sorry.
Everyone, turn to the next page.
Mr. Kong, do I have to stand until the end of the class?
I’ll give you ten minutes to read this page.
Let’s read together.
Ko Song.
What?
Stop talking.
Otherwise, you will be punished again.
My shorts.
What?
Don’t laugh at me.
What are you talking about?
Can you pull my shorts?
I’m studying.
I have a wedgie. It’s itchy. Come on, help me.
Are you serious?
Come on. It’s itchy.
Okay, okay.
What a relief!
Next week, we will have a quiz and a school trip.
What?
You don’t even know where we are going,
but you already get excited.
So where are we going?
Mangrove forest.
Mr. Kong, why don’t we go to Bangkok?
A place with air conditioning
where we can spend time comfortably.
Kids these days.
I can go anywhere.
But right now, can I sit down first?
Everyone, let’s get back to our lesson.
My butt hurts.
Why didn’t you hurry and pull it? It was so itchy.
Because of the wedgie,
I now want to go to the bathroom.
Why are you smiling?
Nothing.
Guys.
I have something to show you.
I prepared lots of snacks today.
So your bag is fat because of the snacks?
What else do you think would be in my bag?
Just eat it.
Just pick anything that you like.
Give me some.
Here.
Look, Tle.
This is how you eat it.
If you eat a snack in the morning, it will spike your blood sugar.
Just eat it.
I’ve been putting up with your stomach growling for a while.
It’s delicious.
Aren’t you excited?
Yes.
But the teacher said the sunlight is strong today.
Are you Dracula?
What?
Come to think about it.
This is our first trip together.
Huh?
What did you say?
This is our first trip together.
Do you like it?
I’ll tell you when we get home.
Fine.
Guys, shall I open a new snack bag?
Sure.
Damn.
It serves you right.
Everyone, get off the bus.
Everyone, stay orderly, please.
Let’s go, Ko Song.
Come on, Ko Song.
Don’t run.
Stay in a line.
Guys, let’s have fun in the mud.
Let’s go.
Hold on, Krittin.
Yes.
Don’t do anything crazy.
Yes, sir.
Go. Follow your friends.
Tle, please help me monitor them.
Sure.
It’s so refreshing.
Why do you look so grumpy?
Come out and feel the sunlight.
Ko Neung.
Huh?
The best time to go out in the sun is 6 – 9 a.m.
Right now, it’s dangerous to be exposed to the sun.
What?
So what are we doing here at this hour?
Are you stupid?
Our meeting time at school is 8 a.m.
With the traveling, that’s why we got here now.
Do you want to compete with me, Augar?
Who can plant more saplings?
You dare to compete with me, the god of competition?
Yes.
You got a deal.
How dare you call yourself that?
What about you, August?
Just leave me out.
I’ll be with Ko Song and Achi.
I’m not an energetic folk like you.
Wear this.
Augar.
Take it.
It’s okay.
Wear it.
You look so pale.
Stop arguing with me.
He doesn’t look pale.
His face is all red.
I’m sensitive to sunlight.
That’s right.
Damn, me too.
I should wait in an air-conditioned room.
Ko Song, can you take a picture for me?
Damn, why didn’t we bring a camera?
That’s right.
I want to have a picture too.
Get closer.
Tle.
Can you take a picture for us?
I want to have a picture too.
Just one picture.
It’s not my camera.
You need to wait to ask the owner.
Come on, Tle.
Can you take a picture for me?
Okay.
Huh?
But you just said no to me.
Come here, Ko Song.
You have a double standard.
Ready?
One, two, three.
Since you did a great job today.
Your teacher wants to give you a reward.
You will have free time for one hour.
Let’s jump into the sea.
Sure.
We’ve been living in a beach town,
but we’ve never gone to the beach together.
So this will be their hazing.
Shall we?
What do you mean?
August, you take his right. I’ll take his left.
Augar, can you handle it alone?
No problem.
What are you doing? I want to do it too.
August, three, two, one, go.
Wait.
I can’t swim.
Don’t worry.
Trust me.
Okay.
♪ Every time that we meet again ♪
♪ Something grows a little more each day ♪
♪ The closer we are, the more I feel the love I’ve waited for ♪
♪ Might not be too far away at all ♪
My eyes hurt.
♪ Even when winter fades I’ll still wait on ♪
♪ Till the final raindrop falls, hope is never gone ♪
♪ As long as I have you holding my hand as we walk on ♪
♪ I fear nothing if this season has you ♪
I got the answer.
You asked me if I like that we take a trip together.
I really like it.
Why am I always the only one who sees it?
Wow!
This is so cool, Ko.
Do you like it that much?
I don’t want to go to an internet café.
You can come to use it every day.
No, I don’t want to bother you.
It’s not a big deal.
Are you going to sleep?
I’m tired.
I’m going to rest my eyes for 20 minutes.
But you can play the games.
It’s okay to turn on the speaker.
20 minutes?
I have tried it.
I wanted to briefly rest my eyes,
but I ended up sleeping through the night.
Damn it. I’m dead.
What the heck?
Damn it.
You seem to have fun with it.
I thought you were sleeping.
I told you I just rested my eyes.
I do it often while studying.
Studying is so boring, Ko Song.
I’m not surprised. You don’t like studying.
I’m tired of playing games.
Do you have anything else for me to do?
What?
I’m bored.
I’m bored. I’m bored. I’m bored.
Don’t you have something new to do?
If you’re bored, why don’t you go home?
Or do you want to sleep over here?
No.
Can’t you find something for me to play?
Do you want to eat oranges?
I already ate it today. I’ve had enough.
What is it, Ko Song?
What is it?
Let me see.
How does it work?
Am I smart enough to play it?
Ko Song.
Come on.
Come here.
Choose a number.
What is this?
Come on. Choose a number.
One.
How many times?
10 times.
Here we go.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
What?
Be careful.
Say it.
Be careful. Your friend might become your date.
Which friend will it be?
Many of our classmates have a crush on you.
Some kids from other classes also like you.
You are quite popular these days.
Silly. It’s just nonsense.
Believe it or not, but don’t disrespect my prophecy.
This is fun.
Let’s do it again.
Choose a number.
Four.
20 times.
No problem.
Eleven, twelve, thirteen. Fourteen, fifteen, sixteen, seventeen, eighteen, nineteen, twenty.
Among your friends, you will be the first one to date.
See?
Your prophecy is always about dating.
It won’t be true.
You don’t believe me.
I read fortunes for Augar and August.
It said they would have diarrhea in the next three days.
It really happened.
Anyone can do it.
Can you predict what will happen tonight?
Choose a number.
Two.
15 times.
Let’s roll.
Seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen, fifteen.
Your soulmate is on your left.
So your soulmate,
Your life is always about books.
I think it’s pretty accurate.
It’s late.
Will you go home or sleep over here?
If you don’t mind that I won’t take a shower.
Can I sleep over here?
I’m too lazy to go home.
Then I’ll go take a shower.
(To fall in love with someone,)
(It takes only seven seconds.)
(One.)
(Two.)
(Three.)
(Four.)
(Five.)
(Six.)
(Seven.)
♪ Will say "I love you" ♪
♪ Will say "I love you" so you know ♪
♪ No more watching from afar, letting chances go ♪
♪ To make this worth the wait after all ♪
Damn, he kissed me.
My mom told me to give you this orange cake.
How do you know that Ko likes an orange cake?
How could he kiss me and disappear?
What?
You two are acting strange.
How did you get in?
Hold me.